Register of the Garip Sultan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound Recordings, 1967-1991, undated (Boxes 27-33)
  - 1/4 inch sound tape reels (175), 1967-1991
    - 1985
      - "Majit Gafuri: 'The Mosque of Khan'" (Box-tape 31: 19)
      - "R. Faizullin: My Native Language" (Box-tape 31: 20-23)
      - "Säjdäs-Tapsiru" (Box-tape 32: 14)
      - "Hisam Kamalov" (Box-tape 32: 15)
      - "Nuri Arslan- Dingez Jarinda" (Box-tape 32: 17)
      - "Tatar Soviet Islamist on Modification of Islam in Tatar-Bashkiria-Zakat" (Box-tape 32: 19)
      - "Admission Examinations to Higher Educational Institutions: How Many Tatar and Bashkir Students May Enroll Out of Competition Outside Their Republic" (Box-tape 33: 10)
    - 1986
      - "Gabdulla Tuqay Prize Laureate G. Rakhim's Poem 'Lost and Found'" (Box-tape 27: 8)
      - "The Fall of Kazan Khanate - 15th October Anniversary: Reflection of Historical Fate in Soviet Tatar Poetry" (Box-tape 27: 7, 28: 2)
      - "The Fall of Kazan - 434th Anniversary: 1. Historical Excursus 2. Literary - Musical Feature - Excerpts From an Emigre Novel The Queen Suymbike (Box-tape 27: 21)
      - "A. Benningsen's Book Moslems of the Soviet Union (Box-tape 27: 15)
      - "100th Birth Anniversary of the National Poet Gabdulla Tuqay: His Attitude to Islam, His Poems on Islam" (Box-tape 27: 20)
      - "Kommunizmnin Qorbanlari" (Box-tape 27: 22-24)
      - "Songs Written on the Gabdulla Tuqay Poems, Airat Arslanov" (Box-tape 28: 1)
      - "Tatar Life Abroad" (Box-tape 28: 8-10)
      - "National Heritage: Historian A. Battal Tajmas' Contribution to Turko-Tatar Social-Political Thought" (Box-tape 28: 11)
      - "100th Birth Anniversary of the National Poet Gabdulla Tuqay, Impact of His Work on Tatar-Bashkir Culture and Art" (Box-tape 28: 13)
      - "Tatar-Bashkir Chronology - M. Vakhitov: Leader of Muslim Communists During the Revolution and Civil War" (Box-tape 28: 14)
      - "Contemporary Tatar-Bashkir Literature: Laureaute of Tuqay Literary Prize G. Afzal's Poem 'Tatarstan'" (Box-tape 28: 15)
      - "National Poet Gabdulla Tuqay Centenial: Gabdulla Tuqay Laureate Nuri Arslans Poems About 'The Fate of Nation'" (Box-tape 28: 17)
      - "Tatarstan-Nuclear Power Plant in Tatarstan and Writers' Concern" (Box-tape 28: 20)
      - "Religion and Politics: Great Mufti R. Fakhreddin's Historical 'Religious Testament'" (Box-tape 28: 23)
      - "Pillars of Islam: Iman - Declaration of Faith Oneness of God, Reading From Quran" (Box-tape 29: 3)
      - "Korban Bairame - Religious, Social Meaning of Sacrifice" (Box-tape 29: 7, 30: 18)
      - "140th Anniversary of 'The Karvan Saray: Architectural Monument of Bashkir People in Orenburg: Used as Chemical Laboratory'" (Box-tape 30: 1)
      - "Innovator Poet Taktash's 85th Anniversary: Mysticism, Symbolism, Allegory, Realism in His Poetry" (Box-tape 30: 10)
      - "Ramazan Bajram" (Box-tape 30: 20-21)
      - "Analar Kene" (Box-tape 30: 22-23)
      - "100th Birth Anniversary of the National Poet Ğabdulla Tuqay: Soviets Falsify His Philosophy on Religion" (Box-tape 31: 7-8)
      - "Islamic Encyclopedia: Islam and Mercy" (Box-tape 32: 5-13)
      - "'Gali Ilyasi's 130th Birth Anniversary:' Author of the First Tatar Drama" (Box-tape 32: 19)
      - "Tatar - Bashkir Chronology: The Centennial of the Tatar Classic F. Amirkhan" (Box-tape 33: 12)
    - 1987
      - "Shihabutdin Mardjani - Founder of the Tatar National History, Muslim Scholar of the XIXth Century,", 1987 November 7, 1988 February 2 (Box-tape 27: 10-11)
      - "The 100th Anniversary of Classic Writer G. Ibrahim, a Victim of Stalinism: Impact of His Works to Central Asian Writers" (Box-tape 27: 6, 30: 11)
      - "The 100th Anniversary of Classic Writer G. Ibrahim, a Victim of Stalinism: Rehabilitated, but Whole Truth Still Not Told; Memoirs of Prof. Makhamatova" (Box-tape 27: 5, 30: 7)
      - "H. Tufan's Poetry - Victim of Stalinism" (Box-tape 28: 19)
      - "'Glasnost' and Literary History: Why the XIVth Century Tatar Poem 'Idegey' Still Prohibited?" (Box-tape 28: 25)
      - "Bookshelf. Boris Ishholdin's Book: How Russian Historians Evaluate the Period of Tatar Domination in Russia" (Box-tape 29: 1)
      - "Tatar Samizdat: R. Vefali, Literature-Religious Lyric 'The Wine of Death'" (Box-tape 29: 5)
      - "National Heritage-Culture: The First Tatar Opera Sania and the Fate of Its Composer" (Box-tape 30: 14)
      - "80th Anniversary of the First Tatar Social-Democratic Paper Ural" (Box-tape 30: 15)
      - "Analar Kene" (Box-tape 30: 24)
      - “Victims of Stalinism: Some Unpublished Verses by Fätkhi Bürnash" (Box-tape 31: 25)
      - "Tatar Theologician and Muftii R. Fakhretdin - Victim of Stalinism" (Box-tape 31: 2)
      - "The Meaning of Hajj - Pilgrimage to Mecca" (Box-tape 32: 20)
      - "National Heritage - Culture: 100th Anniversary of the First Tatar Drama: G. Ilysi's Poor Girl" (Box-tape 33: 11)
    - 1988
      - "National Heritage - History Forbidden Word - The Fall of Kazan: The 436th Anniversary, a Literary-Musical Show" (Box-tape 27: 15)
      - "White Spots; Rewriting of Bashkir ASSSR's History: Truth About Fate of Poet Sh. Babich (First Victim of Communism)" (Box-tape 28: 18)
      - "Youth Program: Literary-Musical Show: 'Native Language' Theme in Contemporary Tatar Poetry" (Box-tape 29: 4)
      - "Contemporary Tatar Literature: F. Husni's Controversial Novel About Collectivisation of Agriculture The 1930's" (Box-tape 30: 9)
      - "Tatar Life Abroad: Emigre Poetry: Sh. Nigmati's Lyrical Verses" (Box-tape 31: 24)
    - 1989
      - "Cultural Heritage and 'Glasnost': Political Controversy Over Rehabilitation of G. Iskhaqi: 1. His Literary Heritage, 2. His Contribution to Tatar Press" (Box-tape 27: 9)
      - "Gayaz Iskhaki" (Box-tape 27: 14)
      - "Tatar-Bashkir Chronology: 103rd Birth Anniversary of the National Poet Ğabdulla Tuqay: Impact of His Works on National Culture and Art (Literary-Misical Show)" (Box-tape 29: 12)
      - "The Fall of Kazan - 437th Anniversary: Literary-Musical Feature" (Box-tape 31: 1, 31: 9)
    - "Qazannьn Jigilui,", 1990 (Box-tape 29: 8)
    - "Special Feature: 439th Anniversary of Fall of Kazan,", 1991 (Box-tape 29: 6)
  - Sound cassettes (26), unlabeled, undated (Box 33)